moremagic.com 2012-09-20

# More Magic :: Privacy Policy

MoreMagic Solultions, Inc. believes strongly in protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of personal information collected from you through the use of this website.

**Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

We may ask you to submit personal details when requesting a service or information, or participating in a forum or survey. This personal information, which you voluntarily submit, will be used to contact you, or send you information you have requested or that we feel will be of interest to you. We may contact you via phone, email or post. If we send you a promotional or marketing based email, we will include an option to unsubscribe in the email.

**Disclosure of Information**

MoreMagic does not sell or otherwise market personal or confidential information to third parties. We do however use third parties (including contractors and service providers) to help with certain aspects of our business, which may require disclosure of your personal information to them. MoreMagic requires these third parties to use your personal information only to the extent necessary to accomplish the purpose for which your information was submitted. Third parties to whom we disclose information are required to keep your personal information confidential and secure.

**Linked Sites**

Some hyperlinks may be posted on this website that link to other websites not under our control. We are not responsible for, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of each website that you visit.
